[SPEAKER_00]
[SPEAKER_01] Look, now look what I've done.
[SPEAKER_01] What I came up here to tell you is that you must stop phoning me a dozen times a day.
[SPEAKER_00] times a day.
[SPEAKER_01] sending me 20 telegrams.
[SPEAKER_00] All right, a beautiful telegram, don't I? Everybody says so.
[SPEAKER_01] How you gonna listen to what I have to say?
[SPEAKER_00] Look, look, what's the use of fighting, Hildi? I'll tell you what you do. You come back to work on the paper. If you find you can't get along in a friendly fashion, we'll get married again.
[SPEAKER_00] Oh, certainly, I haven't any hard feelings.
[SPEAKER_01] Oh, Lord, you're wonderful in a loathsome sort of way. Now, will you please be quiet just long enough for me to tell you what I came up here to say?
[SPEAKER_00] I have a lunch date already.
[SPEAKER_01] I have a lunch date already. I cannot break this. Will you take your hands on me? What are you playing, osteopath? Temper, temper.
[SPEAKER_00] I can't.
[SPEAKER_00] Break it, break it, break it, take your hand.
[SPEAKER_00]
[SPEAKER_01] I'll listen more. You are no longer my husband and no longer my boss, and you're not going to be my boss.
[SPEAKER_00] What's that supposed to mean?
[SPEAKER_01] just what I say.
[SPEAKER_00] You mean you're not coming back to work on the paper?
[SPEAKER_01]
[SPEAKER_01] All right, Mr. Burns, for the first time today. Ah, got a better...
[SPEAKER_00] You're up, huh?
[SPEAKER_01] You bet I've got a better...
[SPEAKER_00] All right, go on. Take it. Work for somebody else. That's the gratitude I get. Oh, I wish you'd stop panning. One way you went and came here five years ago, a little college girl from a school journalism. I took a dull-faced hick.
[SPEAKER_01] No, I wish you'd stop panicking.
[SPEAKER_01] Well, it wouldn't take me if I hadn't been to office.
[SPEAKER_00] Well, why should I? I told you nobody would have a face around here, man. Good looking at that, but I was shuddering. Listen, Walls, okay? Listen, I made a great reporter out of your healthy image. What we have is good on any other paper in New York. We're a team. That's what we are. You need me and I need Joe in the paper, and he's... Oh!
[SPEAKER_01] Listen, wall. Listen, wall.
[SPEAKER_01] We're a team, that's what we are, you and me, my name's Joe and the better needs both of us!
[SPEAKER_01] seconds.
[SPEAKER_00]